Guide to the Schickel family papers, 1905-1965
Schickel family papers, 1905-1965
- Series I. Business Records
  - Elston, Mrs. Lydia A., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Emblem Mfg. Co., 1936-1940 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Emerson Electric Mfg. Co., 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Ennis Supply Co., 1947, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Equitable Life Assurance Soc. of the U.S., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Errigo, Edward O., 1954 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Eutectic Welding Alloys, Inc., 1953 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Excelsior Motor & Mfg. Co., 1926-1927 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Expenses Connected with Meetings, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - "F" Misc., Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Fabric Body Corp., 1926 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Fairfield Laboratories, Inc., 1958 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Fairview Associates, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Fairview, 1936-1940 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Fairview Manor Account Numbers, Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Fairview Manor Annual Report, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - (F.H.A.)-Fairview Manor, 1943-06-1947-06 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - (F.H.A.) - Fairview Manor, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Fairview Manor Realty Co. Inc, Bank Statements, 1945-1947 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Fast, Edward N., Fidelity Title & Trust Co., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Fedders Manufacturing Co., Undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - F.H.A. - Fairview Manor, 1938-1940 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - F.H.A. - Fairview Manor, 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - F.H.A. - Fairview Manor - Letters of approval, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - F.H.A. NYC property, 236 E. 24th St., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Fairview Manor - F.H.A., 1940 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - F.H.A. - Fairview Manor, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Fairview Manor Statements, Undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - F.H.A. (Before June, 1939), 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - F.H.A. letters of request, 1946-1961 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - F.H .A., Buffalo - application for mortgage ins., 1946-1951 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - F.H.A., Buffalo - application for priority, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - F.H.A., Fairview, Washington, Buffalo (after June, 1939), 1956, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - F.H.A., Danby Road, 1956-1959 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - F.H.A., Elmcrest Circle, 1950-1955 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - (Fed. Rent Control) The Housing Expediter, 1947-1952 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Federal Wage-Hour Law, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Federation of NY taxpayers, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Feeks & Rutz, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Feinberg, Abraham W., 1936 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Fenestra, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Fennel & Dimenstein, Undated (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Fessenden, Kenealy & Ryan, Undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Fidelity Title & Trust Co., 1920, 1928-1932 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Fidelity Title & Trust Co., 1925, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Fifth Avenue BanK, 1925-1935 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Finger Lakes Drama Festival (CYO), 1947 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Finn, R. K., 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - First National Bank of Ithaca, 1946-1954 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - First National Bank of Ithaca, 1932-1933 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - First National Bank of Ithaca, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - First Stamford Nat'l Bank & Trust Co., Undated (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Fitzmaurice, Agnes, Agency, 1937, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Florence Manufacturing Co., 1954 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - FNMA COmmitment Legislation, Undated (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Freeman, Harrop A., 1950, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Freeman's Motor Marine, Undated (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Freeville Concrete Products Co., Inc., Undated (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Friedrich, E. H. Co., Doorbuck, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - "G" Misc., Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - J. D. Gallagher Co., 1957-1962 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Gannon, Rev. Robert I.,S.J., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Gateway Glass Co., Inc., 1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - General Electric, 1934-1940 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - General Electric, 1942-1953 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Gerrity Lumber, 1943-1961 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - General Electric see also Air Conditioning, 1947-1950 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Gertis, Alfred C., 1946-1948 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Gleason, Daniel J., 1938 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Glendening, w. C., 1937 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Glens Falls Indemnity Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Glens Falls Ins. Co., 1943-1961 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Globe Indemnity Co. Dr., 1935 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - G.L.F. Coop. all depts., 1946-1954 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - G.L.F. Coop. all depts., 1955-1960 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Golder, Arthur J., 1959-1961 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Goldfarb Flower Shops, 1946-1958 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Government Printing Office, 1929-1962 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Great Lakes Carbon Corp., 1951-1954 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Great Lakes Steel Corp., 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Green, Thomas F., 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Green, Stephen, Co., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Groban Supply Co., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Guerity Company, Inc., The, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - "H" Misc., Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Halperin, J. & Co., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Hampton Roads Realty Corp., 1952-1955 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Hanover Bank, The, 1945, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Hardee, Dicky D., 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Hardee, Patricia A., 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Hartell, John A., 1937 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Hasbrouck, S. K., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Hasco Machinery Co., 1942 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Hatch, Ira & Mildred S., 1937 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Hatfield, H. G., Electric Corp., 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Hawkins, James M., Corp., 1948-1954 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Hayden Crocker Co. see also Kewanee Mfd. Co. & Wholesale Service Supply Co., 1955 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Hearing Aids, Undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Barbara Hedges, Undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Heiskell, Mr. Andrew, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Hemphill, Noyes & Co., 1933 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Higgins & Zabriskie, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Higgins Industries, Inc., 1953-1959 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Hilton Hotel - San Antonio, Texas, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Horne Builders Assoc. of Finger Lakes, Inc., 1952-1963 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Horne Builders Assoc. of Finger Lakes, Inc. see B. M. Clarey, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Horne Builders Assoc., Inc. Life Insurance, 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Horne Building Industry Presentation, Inc., 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Horne Building Plan Service, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Horn, A. C., Co. (Horn Keramik), 1936-1939 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Horn, A. C., Co. (Horn Keramik), 1950-1956 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Horowitz, Mrs. M., 1936 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Horowitz Bros, Undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Henry Ford Hospital, Undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Hough, B. K., 1950-1954 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Hough Shade Corp., 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - House & Horne, 1953-1958 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Housing Survey G. E. Adv.-Elec. Lab Housing, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Housing Survey Ithaca - By Prof. W. A. Anderson, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Hungerford, U. T., Brass & Copper Co., 1926-1927 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Huther Bros. Saw Mfg. Co., Inc., 1948-1954 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Hutto Eng. Co., 1929-1933 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Hydrawlik Co. see Plura (?) Plastics, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - I, J Misc., Undated (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - IBM, Owego, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - IBM Electric Typewriter Div., 1964 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Illmer, Louis, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Immaculate Conception Church, 1947-1954 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Immaculate Conception Church, 1948-1952 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Immaculate Conception Church, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Imperial Brass Mfg. Co., 1929-1932 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Inglehart, Donald, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Information requests, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Inquiries for Apts (by mail), 1963 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Inquiries for Catalogs, List Price, etc., 1946-1950 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Inquiries: Corres., 1955-1959 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Inquiries: Drafting Room Equipment, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Inquiries: Electrical Equipment, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Inquiries - Index, 1939-1954 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Inquiry, Letters of, about Materials, 1926-1938 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Inquiries and Replies, 1951-1954 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Inquiries - Special Products, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Inquiries and Answers, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Inquiries & Answers, 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Inquiries & Answers, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Catalog Requests, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Insto-Gas Corp., 1956 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Insurance Co. of North America, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Inter-Office Memos, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - International Register Co., 1940-1957 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Intrusion - Prepakt, 1946-1948 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Invoices for Extra Services, 1940-1942 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Irving Trust Co., 1948-1955 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Irvington Form & Tank Corp., 1946-1954 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Ithaca Chamber of Commerce, 1941-1954 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Ithaca Chamber of Commerce, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Ithaca College, 1951-1954 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Ithaca Common Council, 1948-1961 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Ithaca, City of, 1951-1958 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Ithaca, City of - Public Works Dept, 1955-1959 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Ithaca Defense Rental Area, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Ithaca Enterprises, Inc., 1936-1947 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Ithaca Journal, 1936-1948 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Ithaca Journal, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Ithaca Journal - stenographer, 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - [Ithaca] Journal, Letters to the - Ithaca Public Housing Project, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Ithaca Loan Finance, Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Ithaca Propane Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Ithaca Real Estate Board, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Ithaca Real Estate Board, Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Ithaca Savings Bank, 1938-1958 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Ithaca Savings & Loan Assoc., 1942-1960 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Ithaca Traffic Commission - letter re Traffic, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Jackson's Mantel & Grate Works, Inc., 1938-1939 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Jamieson-McKinney Co., 1943-1962 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Janitor, 1940-1941 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Joachim, William F., 1931 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Johansson, C. E., Inc., 1929-1931 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Johnson, B. R., 1940-1955 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Johnson, Sidney K. see also CYO Entrance, 1950-1954 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Jones Appliance Center, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - "K" Misc., Undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Kaiser Aluminum & Chemical Corp., 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Kapner Hardware Inc., 1955 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Kappenberg, Ada L., 1941-1942 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Kelly & Maher, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Kelley Bros., 1956-1956 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Kelly Reamer Co., 1932, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Kelsey-Hayes Wheel Co., 1946 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - The Kent Co., Inc., 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Kimball & Palmer, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Kindt-Collins Co., 1941-1963 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - King, Albert, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Klein & Gmahle, 1929-1932 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Knight Paving Products, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Knights of Columbus, 1947-1959 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Knowles, Thaddeus E., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Kreig Inc., 1954 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Kwik-Kut Carbide Service Co., Inc., 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - "L" Misc., Undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Lake Drive Products Co., Undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Lakow, Samuel & Son, Undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - La Salle Research Corp., 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Layman's Retreat League, 1947-1950 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Lead Industries Assoc., 1951-1961 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Lee & Judson, Att'ys., 1941 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Lee, D. Boardman, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Legislation-Housing, letters to Gov. Rockefeller, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Lehigh Valley House Meeting, Undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Leipzig Spring Fair, 1935-1937 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - LeMoyne College, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Lenox Furnace Co., 1941, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Le Tourneau, R. G., Inc., 1946 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Letter from Cornell, 1946-1948 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Letters to be answered, Undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Le Valley, McLeod, Kinkaid Co., Inc., 1938-1954 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Licenses - NY Dept. of State & Dept. of Education, Undated (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Life Extension Examiners, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Life Magazine, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Lilley-Ames Co., The, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Lincoln National Bank & Trust Co., 1938, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Lith-I-Bar Co., 1954 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Littleford Bros., 1937 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Long's Distributors, Inc., 1955 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Loring, Malcolm S., Undated (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Loyola School, 1930-1932, 1952-1957 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Loyola University, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Lucas, J. L. & Son, Inc., 1942 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Lucente, Rocco P., 1958 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Luxor Carpet Co., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Lyon Metal Products, Inc., 1941, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - "M" Misc., Undated (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Maas & Waldstein Co., 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - MacDaniels, Mrs. L. H., Undated (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - MacNeil Mitchell, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Magnus Chemical Co., Undated (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Mall Tool Co., 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Otto T. Mallery, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Manning, Eugene, 1950, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Manning, H. A., Co., 1950, 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Mansville, Johns-, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Manufacturers Trust Co., 1941-1945 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Manufacturers Trust Co., 1945-1953 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Marine Midland Trust Co. of New York, 1938-1941 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Marietti, Mario E., 1937 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Marsh, James P. & Co., 1929-1932 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Masonite Corp., 1936-1947 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Massachusetts Bonding & Insurance Co., 1943 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Master Builders Co. (Wall Finish), 1936-1939 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Masterson, Mrs. M. L., 1931 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Materials Stock List, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - May Department Store, 1946-1957 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - M and G. Envelope Co., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - McCord Radiator & Mfg. Co., 1930-1932 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - McCready, John H., 1927-1933 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - McKinney Ins. Agency, 1953-1959 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - McKinney Manufacturing Co., 1939 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - McLean, James W., 1954 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - McPherson, A. H. & Son, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Fred Medart Mfg. Co., 1941 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Medico Electric Motor Co., 1953 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Metals Disintegrating Co., Inc., 1953 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Metropolital Life Ins. Co., 1929-1938, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Middlebrook & Sincerbeaux, 1926-1934 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Middlebrook & Sincerbeaux, 1935-1941 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Midwest Concealed Bed Corp., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Mid-West Acoustical & Supply Co., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Milcor Steep Company, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Miller, T. G .,Co., 1937-1955 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Milwaukee Gas Specialty Co., 1956-1957 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Minerals Processing Corp., 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Minneapolis-Honeywell Regulator Co., 1956-1959 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Mintz, Aaron G., 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Minwax Co., Inc., 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, 1941-1951 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, 1942-1945 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Information, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Letters, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Mitchell, Joseph Christopher, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - M-L Servicing Inc., 1959-1963 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Modern Crete, Inc., 1950 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Modern Kitchens of Syracuse, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Moltasch, Mrs. Hugo, 1936-1937 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Monteath, J. H. Co., 1928 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Montgomery Ward, 1940-1954 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Montgomery Ward, 1940-1954 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Montillon, Eugene, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Morris Distributing Co., Inc., 1950-1961 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Morse Twist Drill & Machine, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Morse, Robert V., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Mortgage Certificate Buyers & Sellers, etc, Undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Mortgage Corp. of N.Y., 1938-1940 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Mosch, June G., 1958 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Mother Zero, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Motors, Electrical, Fractional of, 1931-1932 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Motor Vehicle Commissioner, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Mott, Seward H., Associates, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Moulds, D., 1939 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Meunch, George, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Mullins Mfg. Co., 1950 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Murphy Door Bed Co., 1936-1954 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Murphy, Mr. James, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Murph,Mr. R. Dean, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Murray, Daniel R., 1960 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - "N" Misc., Undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - National Assoc. of Home Builders, 1948-1953 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - National Assoc. of Home Builders, 1949-1951 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - National Assoc. of Home Builders, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - National Assoc. of Home Builders, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - National Assoc. of Home Builders, 1959-1963 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - National Assoc. of Home Builders, 1954-1959 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - National Assoc. of Home Builders of the U.S., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - NAHB Congressional Banquet, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - NAHB Correspondance, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - National Assoc. of Housing Officials, 1942-1950 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - National Automobile Chamber of Commerce, 1926-1928 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - National Farm Consulting Service, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - National Fire Underwriters, 1932-1939, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - National Housing Center, 1957-1963 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - National Instituteof Real Estate Brokers, 1950-1959 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - National Life Ins. Co., 1938 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - National Public Housing Conference, Inc., 1946-1949 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - National Sales Co., 1957 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Neller, Walter see also Real Estate Devel., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Nelson, Donald, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - New Mexico Institute of Mining & Technology, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - New Process Co., 1945-1959 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - New York Board of Fire Underwriters, 1956-1961 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - New York Life Ins. Co., 1938, 1951-1963 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - New York State Assembly, Undated (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - New York State Building Code, 1953-1961 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - NYS Dept. of Audit & Control, 1943-1946 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - NYS Dept. of Health (includes Tompkins Co. Health Dept, 1954-1959 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - NYS Dept. of Housing & Buildings, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - NYS Dept. of Labor, 1936-1940, 1954-1960 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - NYS Dept. of Public Works, 1950, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - NYS Dept. of Taxation and Finance, 1942-1960 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - NYS Dept. Licenses - Real Estate Div., 1954-1690 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - NYS Education Dept., 1943-1946 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - NYS Electric & Gas Corp., 1933, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - NYS Employment Service, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - NYS Home Builders Assoc., 1951-1957 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - NYS Home Builders Assoc., 1953-1959 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - NYS Horne Builders Assoc. Convention, 1956-1957 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - NYS Home Builders Ins. Trust Fund, 1960-1964 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - NYS Taxation Instructions, 1951-1953 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - NYS Taxation Instructions, 1954-1960 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - New York Telecoin Corp., 1950-1952, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - New York Telephone Co., 1939-1960 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - New York Times, 1954, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Norton Electric, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Northwestern Mutual Life Ins. Co., 1938, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Notre Dame Univ., 1938-1940 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Notre Dame Univ., 1941-1950 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Nursery Stock Corres., 1959 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - National Housing Agency, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - "O" Misc., Undated (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Otis Elevator Co., Undated (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Ovellette, G., Undated (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Owens-Illinois, Owens-Corning, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Owens, J. F., Machinery Co., 1942 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - "P" Misc., Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Pacific Lumber Co., The, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Padua High School, 1950-1951 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Paint-Spray Equipment Corres., 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Painting Materials - Color cards, etc., Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Palmer, Adam R., 1954 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Palley Supply Co., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Panalite Division, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Paper Baler, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Parkay, Inc., 1954-1956 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Parker Appliance Co., 1929-1932 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Pass & Seymour, Inc., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Pay Roll, 1940-1942 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Penn Metal Co., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Pentz, G. Morris, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Pennsylvania, State of, Dept. of Pub. Inst., 1938 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Perfect Circle Co., 1929-1932 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Perfection Stove Co., 1952-1954 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Perkins, Mrs. Erma D., 1941 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Perkins Machine & Gear Co., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Perry Coal Co., 1950 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Perry House, 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Petroleum Heat & Power Co., 1939 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Phippe, Donald, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Pierson, Samuel N., 1925-1938 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co., 1942 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Pittsburgh Steel Co., 1936 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Plextone Corp. of America, Undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Pollack, L. P, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Pootatuck Corp., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Portland Cement Ass'n., 1946-1953 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Postmaster, Ithaca, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Potter-Parsons, Alma H, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Poultry Equipment, 1946-1954 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Pratt & Whitney Aircraft, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Preferred Utilities Mfg. Corp., 1952 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Pritchard & Son, J. G., 1933-1938 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Progressive Sales Agency, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Pronto Broiler Inc., 1951-1954 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Pross, Albert W., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Provident Life & Casualty Ins. Co., 1958 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Prudential Life Ins. Co., 1938 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Pullman Co., 1934-1959 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Pyle, Enos A., Undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - "Q" Misc., Undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Quasi-Arc Inc., 1929 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - "R" Misc., Undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Radio Corp.of America, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Ragona, Arthur, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Rahn, Bell F., 1961 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Rainville Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Real Estate Agents, 1929-1931 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Real Estate Dealers - Stamford, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Real Estate Development, 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Real Estate License Corres. re "finders fees", 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Reid, William H., 1933 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Reidy, Margaret & Thomas, 1929-1942 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Reinagel Lighting Co., 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Rental Progress Reports, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Re-nu-it Corp., 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Reservations - hotels, etc., Undated (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Reynolds Metals Co., 1946, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Rimland, Phillip, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Robinson & Carpenter, 1951-1954 (Box 7, Folder 64)